

Enes BİRİŞİK

Java Developer

I am a Backend Developer. I have experience building Web Applications, Middleware, RESTful APIs using languages and frameworks including Spring Boot, Hibernate, RDBMS and NoSql. I have a strong understanding of fundamental CS concepts like Object Oriented Programming, Aspect Oriented Programming, MVC Architecture, REST, SOAP, CI/CD and TDD as well as experience building software with more modern techniques, service-based architecture, and third-party API integration. I am also extremenly rigorous and perfectionist in my code, excatly as an Backend Developer should be

enesbrsk@hotmail.com

Istanbul, Turkey

github.com/enesbrsk

05070787234

in linkedin.com/in/enes-birişik-094b20168

medium.com/@enesbrsk69

WORK EXPERIENCE

Java Developer Eureko Sigorta

06/2022 - Present

I am involved in the development of Spring Boot and Core Java based back-end projects. The languages and technologies I use within the framework of the company are as follows; Java(8,11), WSO2, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Data, Oracle SQL, MongoDB, Hibernate, JPA, JDBC, Apache Tomcat, Azure, JIRA.

Junior Java Developer Medya Takip Merkezi

08/2021 - 06/2022

I am involved in the development of Spring Boot and Core Java based back-end projects. The languages and technologies I use within the framework of the company are as follows; Java(8,11), WSO2, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Data, Oracle SQL, MongoDB, Hibernate, JPA, JDBC, Apache Tomcat, Azure, JIRA.

Web Developer InternCybersoft

07/2021 - 08/2021 I used HTML, CSS, JavaScript

EDUCATION

Computer EngineerDuzce Univercity

09/2016 - 06/2021

SKILLS

Java (8,11,17) - Spring Boot(2,3) - Spring Data - Spring Security - Spring Cloud - Spring MVC - JSF - JSP - Java EE -WSO2 - Hibernate - JPA - Elasticsearch - JDBC - MongoDB -Apache Kafka - MySQL - PostgreSQL - MSSQL - Git - JIRA -Docker

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Football Field API

I used Spring Framework, Kotin Entegration, H2 Database

Digital Media API

 I used Spring Framework, Redis, MongoDB, Apache Kafka, Solr, MySQL, PostgreSQL

E-Commerce Web Application

- I used Java, JSP, MySQL, Bootstrap

Veterinary Clinic Mobile Application

- I used Java, PHP, Mysql

Social Media Mobile Application

I used Java, Firebase

ACHIEVEMENTS

Java (Basic) Certificate

HackerRank

Problem Solving (Basic) Certificate

HackerRank

SQL (Intermediate) Certificate

HackerRank

LANGUAGES

English

Limited Working Proficiency